Guide to the Daniel Nilva Negatives PHOTOS 067
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Unions.
  - Subseries I:A: AFSCME, Local 1707/District Council 1707, Community and Social Service Agency Employees Union.
    - [District Council] 1707: Membership Meeting, Jan 12, 1961 (Box 1, Item 757)
    - Pickets at Theatre Benefit, May 5, 1961 (Box 2, Item 933)
    - Local Party, Jun 24, 1961 (Box 1, Item 758)
    - [Meeting in a small room (possibly in the Brooklyn Labor Lyceum) of what appears to be union officials with members or potential members, many of them women, some African-American.], Jul 6, 1961 (Box 1, Item 759)
  - Subseries I:B: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Laundry Workers.
    - Laundry Workers Health Center 222 E. 34 Street, [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 798)
    - Laundry Workers Installation [meeting at hotel], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 799)
    - Laundry Workers Joint Board, Cong. [Congressman?] E. Allan, Oct 8, 1956 (Box 1, Item 797)
  - Subseries I:C: American Transport Union.
    - [American Transport Union Protest Rally at New York City Hall][Signs: "American Transport Union Mass Rally;" "Quill Has Got to Go;" "ATU Demands Real Bargaining Election for Representation"], May 23, 1956 (Box 4, Item 642)
  - Subseries I:D: Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Workers International Union.
    - Local 3 H.I.P. [Health Insurance Plan] L.I.C., [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 708)
    - Local 3 H.I.P. [Health Insurance Plan] L.I.C., [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 761)
    - [Local 262 Strike: Krispy Kernels], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 992)
  - Subseries I:E: Bookeepers, Stenographers and Accountants Union, Local 12646.
    - [Copy negative of print] [Bookkeepers, Stenographers, Accountants Union], 1911 (Box 1, Item 536)
    - Globe Strike, [1930s?] (Box 4, Item 602)
    - [Pickets during a lockout by the Margon Corporation, in front of its headquarters at 235 Spring Street, New York City], [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 541)
  - Subseries I:F: Chefs, Cooks, Pastry Cooks and Assistants Union, Local 89.
    - H.I.P. [Portraits of unidentified men (probably union officers)], May 16, 1956 (Box 1, Item 801)
  - Subseries I:G: Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE).
    - Bartenders Membership Meeting, [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 768)
    - Hotel and Restaurant Workers Glucksterns Picketing, Oct 19, 1950 (Box 2, Item 935)
    - Bartenders Thanksgiving, Nov 1, 1951 (Box 1, Item 767)
    - Hotel and Restaurant [?] [Three men (possibly union officials) posed standing and chatting in an office.], [1960s?] (Box 1, Item 763)
    - Sub-subseries 1: HERE, Local 1
      - [Strike: protest "Strike Breakers" outside NBC Studios], Jan 9, 1956 (Box 4, Item 648)
      - Union Label: Mayor Wagner, Lyman G [New York City Mayor Robert Wagner posed with "Miss Union Maid" and her female attendants, inside his office at City Hall, and on the steps outside City Hall; Wagner posed in his office with men (probably union officials) and a proclamation.], Aug 29, 1956 (Box 1, Item 769)
    - Sub-subseries 2: HERE, Local 6
      - Mrs. Felton 3340 Perry Ave., Bronx, wheel chair, Dec 7, 1950 (Box 2, Item 941)
      - Mrs. Felton 3340 Perry Ave., Bronx, wheel chair, Dec 7, 1950 (Box 1, Item 762)
      - Sherry Netherland Party, Dec 10, 1950 (Box 1, Item 764)
      - Hughes [?] Contract Signing, Dec 11, 1950 (Box 1, Item 766)
      - Basketball Team, Commerce High School, Dec 11, 1950 (Box 1, Item 765)
    - Sub-subseries 3: HERE, Local 11
      - Mike Ancone[?] Childs Contract, [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 770)
      - [Portraits], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 709)
      - Meeting, Fraternal Club, [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 771)
    - Sub-subseries 4: HERE, Local 15 (Bartenders)
      - Webster Hall, Kennedy and Wagner, Sep 20, 1964 (Box 1, Item 672)
    - Sub-subseries 5: HERE, Local 16
      - Johnston Shop Meeting [Group portrait: men and women, African American and white], Jun 13, 1950 (Box 1, Item 772)
      - [Membership? Shop? meeting; speakers and audience.], Oct 5, 1950 (Box 1, Item 773)
      - California Signs [Billboard advertising a restaurant called The Californian as "the most fabulous restaurant on the Great White Way!"], Jan 15, 1951 (Box 1, Item 774)
    - Sub-subseries 6: HERE, Local 144
      - [Mass meeting at Capitol Hotel, New York City, in an auditorium with a circular balcony; images include speakers on stage, audience], May 31, 1951 (Box 1, Item 775)
      - Hotel Front Service Employees Union: Membership Meeting, End of Strike, Jun 8, 1951 (Box 2, Item 940)
      - Hotel Front Service Employees Union: Picket line, 25 E. 77th St., Jun 21, 1951 (Box 2, Item 939)
    - Sub-subseries 7: HERE, Local 302 (Cafeteria Employees)
      - [Cafeteria Employees Union] 25th Anniversary, Hotel Diplomat, Feb 4, 1964 (Box 1, Item 670)
    - Sub-subseries 8: HERE, Local 325 (Waiters)
      - City of Hope: [presentation of check and awards], Jun 26, 1951 (Box 2, Item 1018)
  - Subseries I:H: Industrial Insurance Employees Union.
    - Local 1706 [Mass meeting in an auditorium; images include speakers on stage, audience.], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 780)
    - Insurance Agents [Union], Dec 28, 1950 (Box 1, Item 776)
    - Local 1706 Membership Meeting[?], Mar 29, 1951 (Box 1, Item 777)
    - Local 1706 [Mass meeting at Hotel Diplomat, New York City], Jul 13, 1951 (Box 1, Item 779)
    - Local 1706 [Mass meeting at Capitol Hotel, New York City], Nov 8, 1951 (Box 1, Item 778)
  - Subseries I:I: Industrial Workers of the World.
    - Carlo [Tresca] IWW Meeting at Union Square [copy negative of print], Feb 11, 1914 (Box 1, Item 582)
  - Subseries I:J: International Association of Machinists, District 15.
    - H.I.P. [Health Insurance Plan]: Portrait of Thomas Carey, Aug 24, 1956 (Box 2, Item 969)
  - Subseries I:K: International Brotherhood of Longshoremen.
    - John Dwyer with Carey[?] and [Walter] Reuther; B. Slaughter[?] with McGowan[?], Dec 8, 1955 (Box 1, Item 783)
  - Subseries I:L: International Brotherhood of Teamsters.
    - Local 1343: March of Dimes, [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 782)
    - [Madison Square] Garden Meeting: James R. Hoffa, Mar 14, 1960 (Box 1, Item 781)
  - Subseries I:M: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.
    - ILGWU 91 Show Stage Unity House [play], [1930s?] (Box 4, Item 643)
    - Dressmakers, [1940s?] (Box 1, Item 551)
    - Dressmakers, [1940s?] (Box 1, Item 537)
    - ILGWU Delegation 40th Anniversary, [1940?] (Box 4, Item 102)
    - Housing [Opening of Co-op Buildings on Grand St[?] on Lower East Side, New York City. Leaders and other Dignitaries include: David Dubinsky, Eleanor Roosevelt], Oct 22, 1955 (Box 4, Item 645)
    - Local 62: Boat Ride, Aug 12, 1960 (Box 4, Item 646)
    - M. Gross sworn in on Mayor's Commission (Wagner), Jun 8, 1962 (Box 1, Item 754)
  - Subseries I:N: International Longshoremen's Association.
    - Breakwater Beef, [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 674)
    - Gene Sampson, [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 675)
    - [Independent ILA General Meeting at Madison Square Garden], [1950s?] (Box 4, Item 677)
    - ILA, [1950s?] (Box 4, Item 673)
    - Street Scene, Office of ILA, [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 784)
    - ILA District 65 Textile Workers AFSCME Local 1707 [Patients waiting and being examined at ILA-NYSA Medical Center, and medical and dental personnel at work], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 710)
    - New York Waterfront Strike; "Wildcat" Longshore Strike, 1951 (Box 2, Item 945)
    - Communion Breakfast, Apr 26, 1953 (Box 4, Item 669)
    - AFL: Election, 250 Hudson St., Dec 22, 1953 (Box 4, Item 676)
    - AFL: IWD Brooklyn Vote; NLRB[?] Vote, Dec 23, 1953 (Box 4, Item 678)
    - ILA: Communism [Although the caption doesn't indicate it, these are evidently surveillance photographs. They are shot through the windows of an automobile, hidden behind a newspaper (visible in some of the images) and through from the inside of a plate glass window--possibly a store or office--on what appears to be the second story of a building. The images are mostly of a group of burly men in front of a cafeteria or cafe, probably in Brooklyn, possibly by the waterfront.], May 19, 1954 (Box 4, Item 671)
    - Local 99: Education Luncheon, Astor Hotel, Feb 14, 1962 (Box 1, Item 785)
  - Subseries I:O: International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots.
    - Al O'Brien Marine Engineers Benevolent Association, 117 Maiden Lane, [1940s?] (Box 1, Item 540)
  - Subseries I:P: International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, and Machine Workers.
    - NLRB Hearings, [1940s?] (Box 1, Item 539)
    - [Meeting], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 796)
    - State Hearing, Feb 3, 1950 (Box 1, Item 786)
    - G.E. Conference, Belmont Plaza, Mar 3, 1950 (Box 1, Item 790)
    - Westinghouse Conference, Apr 20, 1950 (Box 1, Item 787)
    - Elizabeth, New Jersey, Singer Plant [Includes shots of strike picket line; speakers on street in front of plant, reporters and news photographers.], Aug 30, 1950 (Box 2, Item 943)
    - [General Electric] Strike Conference, Belmont Plaza, Arthur Riordan[?], Sep 1, 1950 (Box 2, Item 942)
    - Sylvania[?] Contract [signing], Sep 11, 1950 (Box 1, Item 788)
    - Convention, Sep 20, 1950 (Box 1, Item 789)
    - Belmont Plaza, Aug 6, 1951 (Box 1, Item 791)
    - Conference -- Belmont Plaza, Oct 16, 1951 (Box 1, Item 792)
    - Conference Belmont Plaza, Lexington -- Sylvania Large Group, Sep 16, 1952-Sep 17, 1952 (Box 1, Item 793)
    - Conference, Belmont Plaza, Apr 18, 1953 (Box 1, Item 794)
    - Carey at Jewish Labor Committee 10th Israel Anniversary, Town Hall, May 19, 1958 (Box 1, Item 795)
  - Subseries I:R: Office Employees International Union, Local 153.
    - Office Workers Demonstration, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 937)
  - Subseries I:S: Playthings and Novelty Workers Union.
    - [Portraits of an unidentified man (probably a union officer)], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 800)
  - Subseries I:T: Retail Clerks International Association.
    - Bonwit Teller Leaflet Distribution, Sep 14, 1949 (Box 1, Item 52)
  - Subseries I:U: Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU).
    - Annual Ball, St. Nicholas Arena, Nov 30, 1947 (Box 1, Item 51)
    - Contract Negotiators, Jul 11, 1951 (Box 1, Item 802)
    - Sub-subseries 1: RWDSU, Local 1-S
      - Local 1-S Membership Meeting, [Oct 1950?] (Box 1, Item 821)
      - Local 1-S, 125 West 33rd St.: NYC Att. Dick Pastor [Meeting in a hotel suite], Feb 20, 1951 (Box 1, Item 803)
      - Local 1-S, Macy's New Yorker (No. Ballroom) [Speaker at podium.], Oct 9, 1956 (Box 4, Item 804)
      - Local 1-S: Macy's Membership Meeting; Welfare Checks Manhattan Center, Jan 8, 1957 (Box 1, Item 805)
      - Local 1-S: Macy's Arbitration, Feb 26, 1957 (Box 1, Item 806)
      - Local 1-S: Macy's Headquarters, 290 7th Ave., Jun 18, 1957 (Box 1, Item 809)
      - Local 1-S: Macy's Arbitration Check and Credit Union, Sep 20, 1957 (Box 1, Item 807)
      - Local 1-S Macy's Credit Union and Dupe "million $" check [Meeting in a private office; ceremonial presentation of check at Credit Union offices.], Sep 24, 1957 (Box 1, Item 808)
      - Local 1-S Talent Group, Jul 9, 1958 (Box 1, Item 810)
      - Local 1-S: COPE [Committee on Political Education] Prizes, Aug 15, 1958 (Box 1, Item 811)
      - Local 1-S: Membership Meeting, Jan 6, 1959 (Box 1, Item 812)
      - Local 1-S: Social Services Graduation, Mar 2, 1959 (Box 1, Item 813)
      - Local 1-S: Macy's Stewards Meeting, New Yorker, Mar 10, 1959 (Box 1, Item 814)
      - Local 1-S Pickets: Beth David Hospital Workers Strike, May 20, 1959 (Box 4, Item 699)
      - Local 1-S: Macy's Strike Arbitration [Separated as Damaged], Jun 26, 1959 (Box 3, Item 1869)
      - Local 1-S: Bond Winner, Jul 8, 1959 (Box 1, Item 815)
      - Local 1-S: Credit Union Committee, Jun 15, 1960 (Box 1, Item 816)
      - Local 1-S: Congolese Visitors, Aug 26, 1960 (Box 1, Item 817)
      - Local 1-S: Augustine Tompkins, Sep 21, 1960 (Box 2, Item 994)
      - Local 1-S: Leaflet Distribution, Macy's, Mar 23, 1961 (Box 1, Item 818)
      - Local 1-S: Macy's Negotiating Committee, Mar 28, 1961 (Box 1, Item 819)
      - Local 1-S: Macy's Contract Vote, Manhattan Center, Apr 8, 1961 (Box 1, Item 820)
    - Sub-subseries 2: RWDSU, Local 3
      - Bloomingdales Local 3, Office Door and Two Men, [1940s?] (Box 1, Item 550)
    - Sub-subseries 3: RWDSU, Local 338
      - Al Levy, Local 338, 1948 (Box 1, Item 55)
      - Arbitration--NY Delicatessen; Local 338, 1948 (Box 1, Item 56)
      - Local 338; Harlem Groups; [Meeting; interior: group portrait of men (union officers?) in front of panel or banner emblazoned with legend, "Laundry Workers."], Mar 18, 1948 (Box 1, Item 57)
      - Local 338, Mr. Midgen Portrait, May 5, 1948 (Box 2, Item 977)
      - Local 338; Brooklyn [Meeting: speakers and audience], Sep 1, 1948 (Box 1, Item 59)
      - Leo Holtzer; Local 338 [Portrait], Nov 17, 1948 (Box 1, Item 60)
      - Local 338; Harlem Party, Oct 27, 1949 (Box 1, Item 58)
      - Local 338 [Fruit and Vegetable Employees Strike], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 824)
      - Local 338 [Portraits], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 832)
      - Local 338 Harlem Opening [celebration], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 825)
      - Local 338 [Worksite] [Food store scene; grocery store clerk waiting on customer.], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 823)
      - Local 338 Comedy Show, [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 836)
      - Local 338 Me[?] Ornstein [Portrait], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 827)
      - Local 338 Meeting, [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 828)
      - Local 338 Al Levy Rand Stores Card Party, [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 826)
      - Local 338 [Portrait of unidentified man.], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 830)
      - Local 338 Arbitration [New Yorker Delicatessen], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 831)
      - Local 338 [Appears to be union officers and members meeting.], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 833)
      - Local 338; Al Levy, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 973)
      - Local 338 Retail, etc, Feb 16, 1955 (Box 1, Item 822)
    - Sub-subseries 4: RWDSU, Local 474
      - Local 474 [Meeting in ballroom and auditorium in hotel; portrait and group shots at same event.], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 882)
    - Sub-subseries 5: RWDSU, Local 1102
      - Local 1102, 204 W 55 St [Meeting], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 835)
    - Sub-subseries 6: RWDSU, Local 1250
      - [Locals 1250 and 5] [Office Door 2 Men], [1940s?] (Box 1, Item 538)
  - Subseries I:V: Seafarers' International Union.
    - [Copy shots of demonstrators (probably union members) clashing violently with police.], undated (Box 1, Item 843)
    - Seafarers, [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 649)
    - Barcelona SIU, [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 599)
    - Seafarers' International Union Meeting, Apr 23, 1947 (Box 1, Item 54)
    - [Two identical copy shots of a street scene. Appears to show workers during a strike or labor disturbance. Smoke (possibly teargas), a policeman on horseback, and people running.], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 838)
    - [Copy Shots -- Seafarers, Interior of Ship.] [Worksite. Interior of a ship, seamen. Includes duplicates. Probably shot to illustrate poor living and working conditions on shipboard.], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 839)
    - [Copy shot -- men, bunk beds.], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 840)
    - [Copy shots of] Strike 1950 S.I.U. ties up 9 ships at Staten Island Piers (Box 2, Item 948)
    - Copy shots -- Seafarers [The ship "Oregonian" docked at pier; men sitting on the dock in front of the ship.], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 846)
    - [Copy shot of print -- Maritime Federation Kitchen No. 1], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 842)
    - SIU [Exterior. Two men descending stairs/gangplank on side of a docked freighter.], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 711)
    - [Copy shots of prints: New York Port Society -- Street Scene], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 844)
    - [Copy shots -- Seafarers -- Street demonstration], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 845)
    - [Two identical copy shots of men fighting on a wharf--possibly strikebreakers against union members.], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 847)
    - [Copy shot of print: people -- men in mess hall], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 841)
  - Subseries I:W: Textile Workers Union of America.
    - [Union officers meet with rank and file members? Members examine TWUA literature.], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 850)
    - Pollack and Stevenson [Meeting in hotel suite. Principally showing two men—presumably Pollack and (Adlai?) Stevenson.], Sep 1956 (Box 1, Item 849)
    - Christmas Party for Children, Dec 22, 1956 (Box 1, Item 848)
  - Subseries I:X: Transport Workers Union of America.
    - IT Award [Man being presented award.], Aug 11, 1949 (Box 1, Item 61)
    - [Broadcast on WOR-TV Channel 9 (press conference?) with Michael Quill and others (TWU officials? members? some appear to be uniformed bus drivers or subway conductors) seated at a table, with a Transport Workers Union of America banner on wall behind them. Television camera and a microphone are visible in some shots.], [1950s?] (Box 4, Item 682)
    - [Victory Celebration], [1960s?] (Box 4, Item 681)
    - [Local 501: American Airlines Strike], [1960s?] (Box 4, Item 700)
    - [Interviews], Jan 12, 1962 (Box 4, Item 680)
  - Subseries I:Y: United Automobile Workers of America.
    - Homer Martin, President, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 976)
    - [Richard Frankensteen?], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 962)
    - Sub-subseries 1: District 65
      - District 65 Textile Workers; AFSCME Local 1707 [film wallet 3-3] [nitrate], undated (Box not specified, Item 10147)
      - District 65 Textile Workers; Local 1707 [film wallet #3-1] [nitrate], undated (Box not specified, Item 10145)
      - District 65 Textile Workers; AFSCME Local 1707 [Film wallet 3-2] [nitrate], undated (Box not specified, Item 10146)
      - District 65 Textile Workers; AFSCME Local 1707 [film wallet 3-6] [nitrate], undated (Box not specified, Item 10149)
      - District 65 Textile Workers; AFSCME Local 1707 [film wallet #3-4] [nitrate], undated (Box not specified, Item 10148)
      - District 65: Ralph Bellamy Interview, [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 717)
      - District 65: Interview with Sammy Davis Jr. Gotham Hotel, 136 W. 55th, Jul 24, 1956 (Box 1, Item 712)
      - District 65, International Teachers [group visiting (?) at District 65 headquarters], Aug 3, 1956 (Box 1, Item 829)
      - District 65: Medical Society Luncheon, Jun 20, 1957 (Box 1, Item 851)
      - District 65: N.A.A.C.P., Nov 5, 1958 (Box 1, Item 713)
      - District 65: Retiree Violet Baily; [Separated as Damaged], Oct 2, 1959 (Box 3, Item 1871)
      - District 65 [RWDSU on Strike], [1960s?] (Box 4, Item 679)
      - District 65: Stern's Registration [Separated as Damaged], Feb 18, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1870)
      - District 65; by Meeting; St Ann's Church [Separated as Damaged], Feb 19, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1867)
      - District 65; Rehearsal; Barbizon Plaza, Feb 22, 1960 (Box 3, Item 1872)
      - District 65: Community Conference on Race Relations, Mar 11, 1960 (Box 1, Item 852)
      - District 65:Youth Conference Headquarters, Mar 13, 1960 (Box 1, Item 714)
      - District 65: On Way to Forand Bill Meeting [At Manhattan Center], Mar 23, 1960 (Box 1, Item 853)
      - District 65: Shop Presentation of Plaque, May 25, 1960 (Box 1, Item 854)
      - District 65: Pre Labor Day T.V. Broadcast, [Sep 4, 1960?] (Box 1, Item 716)
      - District 65: Women's Committee Cocktail Party, Sep 9, 1960 (Box 1, Item 715)
      - District 65: Neuberger[?] Speaks to NY Society for Ethical Culture, Oct 19, 1960 (Box 1, Item 855)
      - District 65 Dance Class, Roseland, Apr 14, 1961 (Box 1, Item 856)
      - District 65: Congressman [Emanuel] Celler's Office, Apr 21, 1961 (Box 1, Item 857)
  - Subseries I:Z: United Furniture Workers of America (UFWA).
    - [Small meeting of union officers? Includes group portrait.], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 860)
    - First Retired Members, Jun 11, 1956 (Box 1, Item 858)
    - Craftsmen at Scala Shop, Jun 26, 1958 (Box 2, Item 859)
  - Sub-subseries 1: UFWA, Local 76B
    - Furniture Local 76B Dance, Feb 8, 1952 (Box 2, Item 861)
    - Local 76 Picketing Plant -- Mass Picketing 102 St. 5 Ave., Mar 19, 1953 (Box 2, Item 862)
    - Local 76 Labor Board Election, Chesterfield Furniture, Mar 27, 1953 (Box 2, Item 863)
    - Local 76B Installation, Apr 22, 1953 (Box 2, Item 864)
    - Local 76: M. Singer [& Sons] Strike, Sep 23, 1953 (Box 2, Item 865)
    - Local 76 Committees, Dec 8, 1953 (Box 2, Item 866)
    - Local 76B Committtees, Nov 1956 (Box 2, Item 868)
    - Local 76[B] Election, [Jan 16, 1956?] (Box 2, Item 877)
    - Local 76: Tony Vitrone [Portrait], Sep 11, 1956 (Box 2, Item 867)
    - [Local 76B portraits] De Cicco, Mar 28, 1957 (Box 2, Item 869)
    - [Local 76B] De Cicco Testimonial, Apr 6, 1957 (Box 2, Item 870)
    - Local 76: Ben Kreiselman Signs [members displaying informational picket signs.], May 23, 1957 (Box 2, Item 871)
    - [Local 76B]: Blood Bank, Aug 1, 1957 (Box 2, Item 872)
    - Local 76[B] Committee, Mar 4, 1958 (Box 2, Item 873)
    - Local 76: Blood Bank, Apr 10, 1958 (Box 2, Item 875)
    - Local 76[B]: Signing Contract, Apr 16, 1958 (Box 2, Item 874)
    - Local 76[B]: Strike Meeting, Sep 4, 1958 (Box 2, Item 876)
    - Sub-subseries 2: UFWA, Local 102
      - Local 102: Steinway Lodge Pension Checks, Mar 31, 1953 (Box 2, Item 878)
  - Subseries I:AA: United Shoeworkers of America.
    - [Large meeting or conference] Joint Council #13, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 879)
  - Subseries I:BB: United Store and Allied Products Workers.
    - Store Workers: New Yorker [Hotel], J. Carey Speaking, Sep 21, 1955 (Box 2, Item 891)
    - Store Workers [constitutional convention]: New Yorker [Hotel], J. Carey Speaking, Sep 21, 1955 (Box 2, Item 880)
  - Subseries I:CC: United Textile Workers of America.
    - [United Textile Workers of America convention at] Hotel McAlpin, NYC, Oct 22, 1956 (Box 2, Item 881)
    - Local 229 Christmas Party, Regional Office, 129 Lexington, Dec 21, 1957 (Box 1, Item 718)
- Series II: Labor Organizations.
  - Subseries II:A: American Federation of Labor.
    - AFL Convention Atlantic City, 1935 (Box 4, Item 97)
    - [Broadcast] 58th St. Studio [at A.B.C. Studio], May 29, 1947 (Box 2, Item 883)
    - Broadcast; 58th St. Studio, May 29, 1947 (Box 1, Item 53)
    - Statler-NY [Appears to be have been shot at the AFL-CIO merger convention at the Statler-Hilton Hotel in New York City. Includes numerous union leaders (negative 686-30 shows David Dubinsky, for example).], Dec 1, 1955 (Box 4, Item 686)
    - AFL convention (1--13) 12-1 (1--12) 12-2, Dec 1, 1955-Dec 2, 1955 (Box 2, Item 884)
    - United Garment Workers of America Nashville Convention, 1914 (Box 6, Item 12058)
      Historical Note
      United Garment Workers of America union was affiliated with the American Federal Labor.
  - Subseries II:B: American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO).
    - Meeting, Commodore Hotel, Jun 8, 1950 (Box 2, Item 885)
    - United Labor Commission, AFL-CIO Election UJZ TV, Nov 3, 1952 (Box 4, Item 687)
    - AFL-CIO Convention 1st Day; Labor Daily AFL- CIO Convention 2nd Day; AFL-CIO Convention 3rd Day; AFL-CIO Convention 4th Day; Radio Liberator; End Empty Hall; Unity Convention Eleanor Roosevelt; Puerto Rican Delegates; City of Hope, Zimmerman and Williams; Kenosha[?] Labor K, Att. Harold J. Newton, Dec 5, 1955-Dec 8, 1955 (Box 2, Item 886)
    - AFL-CIO Convention [Speakers include: Eleanor Roosevelt, George Meany], Dec 7, 1966-Dec 8, 1966 (Box 4, Item 688)
    - AFL-CIO Unemployment Office, Jun 25, 1958 (Box 2, Item 887)
    - AFL-CIO Meeting Manhattan Hotel on Behalf of G.E. Strike, IUE District 4[?], Oct 19, 1960 (Box 2, Item 888)
    - AFL-CIO Eastern Region Education Conference Shelbourne Hotel, Apr 25, 1961 (Box 2, Item 890)
  - Subseries II:C: American Commission on Africa.
    - American Commission on Africa: Arrival of Students, Sep 10, 1959 (Box 4, Item 683)
  - Subseries II:D: American Labor Education Service.